# LOGAN COLLINS

# Senior Full Stack Developer

+1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

#### **Brewlabs**

**=** 04/2023 - 03/2024

Phttps://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Created UI kit and unit test script to expedite front-end development for landing pages and on-chain services such as staking
- Developed a bot to fetch cryptocurrency assets and price history to show in the TradingView Chart

# Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

#### SparkWorld\*

**=** 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Worked in the front-end development team of 5 members to build the company landing page in React
- Led a team of four front-end developers to develop the front-end of NFT Marketplace and Aggregator using the test-driven development approach
- Developed a bot to get NFT sale data and metadata from other NFT Marketplaces on Avalanche and store them in MongoDB as a subproject of NFT Aggregator
- Developed RESTful APIs and provided Swagger documentation to get sale data and update transaction history

# Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

#### Satang Technologies

**#** 04/2020 - 03/2022

Phttps://satang.com/

- Collaborated with a designer to create a modern, yet simple user interface for our company's landing page
- Designed and developed Firo Bridge to synchronize data between the Firo chain and FiroVM chain and store transaction data in PostgreSQL database to enable Smart Contracts on Firo like Ethereum
- Led Asset Tokenizer project and collaborated with Smart Contract engineer to utilize real-estate transactions on chain

#### Senior Full Stack Developer

#### **Polisport**

**=** 04/2019 - 03/2020

https://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Developed RESTful APIs to retrieve products and services data and implemented pixel-perfect frontend in React from Figma Design
- Wrote unit test scripts for the front-end using Mocha and Jest libraries
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and implemented main UI in React and virtual tour in 3d environment using Three.js library

### Full Stack Developer

#### **Canary Technologies**

**=** 04/2016 - 03/2019

Phttps://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company's culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I created smooth and visually appealing user interfaces as a front-end developer
- Designed MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

## **SUMMARY**

A seasoned full-stack developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry. What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Computer** Science

GPA

**DePaul Unversity** 

3.9 / 4.0

# **SKILLS**

Frontend				
React	Redux	Next.js	Vue	Lit
Bootstrap Tai		wind CSS	Web3	
Backend				
Node.js	Expre	ss.js Go	olang	
Laravel				
Language	S			
JavaScri	pt Ty	peScript	РНР	
Databases	3			
MongoDI	B My	SQL Pos	stgreSQL	
Developm	ent & Op	perations		
Scrum	Agile			
Version Control Systems				
Git G	itHub	GitLab	Bitbucket	<u>:</u>

**Cloud Services** 

**AWS** Microsoft Azure **GCP**